

☑ noelcedrix@yahoo.com

**3** 0995-295-6110

A Obando, Bulacan

www.linkedin.com/in/noelcedrixjoaquin

#### **SKILLS**



## **LANGUAGES**

- Filipino
- English

#### **INTERESTS**

- Anime
- Tekken
- Figure Collecting
- Toy Photography

# Noel Cedrix Joaquin

**Application Support Engineer** 

Application Support Engineer with over 2 years of experience in areas such as L1 Support and UI Development. Team player with exposure in working with local and international colleagues. Highly motivated in learning new tools and technologies.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **Application Support Engineer (L1)**

Accenture Inc. – Cigna Bruin

06/2021 - Present

- Technologies utilized: Domino Data Lab, ServiceNow, Python, SQL, Confluence, GitHub, Dash, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Intercom and Dynatrace
- Primary contact of support to over 1700 data scientists and engineers in helping solve problems related to Domino Data Lab, data/platform access, and code.
- Create and maintain existing Confluence pages for tracking Jira user stories and documenting common platform issues that also acts as L1 Support runbook.
- Lead Python developer for ticket dashboard proof-of-concept for metrics reporting that will be consumed by managers and stakeholders.
- Design and integrate custom bot within Domino Data Lab using Intercom to assist users in resolving common types of issues without submitting a ticket.
- Collaborate with engineering team in setting up Dynatrace synthetic alerts to proactively monitor outages within Domino Data Lab.
- Demonstrate new or common recurring issues, workarounds, and best practices within Domino Data Lab to stakeholders during bi-weekly open forums.
- Created learning materials and trained 2 newly onboarded resources within L1 Support Team.

## **UI Developer**

Accenture Inc. – Cigna Innovation Prod Support

03/2021 - 04/2021

- Technologies utilized: C#, ASP.NET Core MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and MS SQL Server
- Codes according to design specification to produce required functionality.
- Research and implementation of database integration for fetching test data.
- Provide support to senior developers during testing and provision of test data.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering**

Adamson University

06/2013 - 01/2020

# **TRAININGS**

## **Data and Analytics Bootcamp**

Accenture Inc. 01/2021 – 03/2021

**Complete Python Bootcamp: From Zero to Hero in Python** 

Udemy 06/2020